<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="Iagree">I agree to</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="agreement_tip">Please agree to TermofService and PrivacyPolicy</string>
    <string name="already_bind">This email address has already been taken</string>
    <string name="and"> and </string>
    <string name="app_name">HtLoginSdk</string>
    <string name="bind">Bind Account</string>
    <string name="bind_fail">Failed. please try again</string>
    <string name="bind_name_empty">Please choose an account first</string>
    <string name="bind_success">Binding Succeeded</string>
    <string name="bind_title">Bind Account</string>
    <string name="delete_tip">are you sure to delect?</string>
    <string name="delete_tip_title">Tip</string>
    <string name="empty_email">Please enter a valid email address</string>
    <string name="error_password">Wrong Password</string>
    <string name="forget_password">Please check your email to reset your password</string>
    <string name="forgetpassword">Forgot password?</string>
    <string name="found">Password Recovery</string>
    <string name="illegal_length_tip">Username should be 6 to 32 characters long</string>
    <string name="illegal_password">Password cannot contain space or special characters</string>
    <string name="illegal_pwd_tip">A password should include 6 to 16 characters</string>
    <string name="illegal_uname_tip">Please enter a valid email address</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="loginBack">Please login first</string>
    <string name="login_account_edit_hint">Email Address</string>
    <string name="login_fail">Login failed. please try again</string>
    <string name="login_name_empty">Please choose an account first</string>
    <string name="login_password_edit_hint">Password</string>
    <string name="login_success">Login succeeded</string>
    <string name="login_success_orher">ogin succeed. Please bind your account as soon as possible to prevent any data lost</string>
    <string name="network">Network Error</string>
    <string name="not_suginup">Account dosent exist</string>
    <string name="null_email_or_password_tip">UserName and Password can not be Null</string>
    <string name="privacy_clause">We are dedicated to protecting the privacy rights of our users. This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) describes the ways we collect, store, use, and manage the information that you provide or we collect in connection with our game provided (collectively, the "Service"). Please note that we are not responsible for the actions of third party people or companies, the content of their sites, the use of information you provide to them, or any products or services they may offer. Any link to those sites does not constitute our sponsorship of, or affiliation with, those people or companies. By using the Service, you are expressing your agreement to this Policy and the processing of your data, including your personal information, in the manner provided in this Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use the Service. Our primary goals in collecting and using information is to create your account, provide Services to you, improve our Service, contact you, conduct research and create reports for internal use. we may collect and record certain information such as your unique device ID, hardware type, media access control address, international mobile equipment identity , the version of your operating system , your device name, your email address, and your location (based on your Internet Protocol address). This information is useful to us for troubleshooting and helps us understand usage trends. In addition, we create a unique user ID to track your use of our Service. This unique user ID is stored in connection with your profile information. Facebook and Google+ Connect You can log in to our site using sign-in services (“SN Service”) such as Facebook or Google+. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name, email address, and resume to pre-populate our sign up form. The information we collect when you connect your user account to an SN Service may include: (1) your name, (2) your SN Service user identification number and/or user name, (3) locale, city, state and country, (4) sex, (5) birth date, (6) email address, (7) profile picture or its URL . Push Notifications We may send you push notifications through our mobile applications to send you game updates and other service related notifications that may be of importance to you. You may at any time opt-out from receiving these types of communications by turning them off at the device level through your settings. Third Party Services Our services may contain third party tracking tools from our service providers, examples of which include Google Analytics and Appsflyer. Such third parties may use cookies, APIs, and SDKs in our services to enable them to collect and analyze user information on our behalf. The third parties may have access to information such as your device identifier, MAC address, IMEI, locale (specific location where a given language is spoken), geo-location information, and IP address for the purpose of providing their services under their respective privacy policies. Our privacy policy does not cover the use of tracking tools from third parties. We do not have access or control over these third parties. Disclosure of Your information We do not share your personal information except as approved by you or as described below: •	With your consent, for example, when you agree to our sharing your information with other third parties for their own marketing purposes subject to their separate privacy policies.  •	We may release your information as permitted by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or when we believe that release is appropriate to comply with the law; investigate fraud, respond to a government request, enforce or apply our rights; or protect the rights, property, or safety of us or our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection. Security Although we make good efforts to store the information collected on the Service in a secure operating environment, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of that information during its transmission or its storage on our systems.  Further, while we attempt to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party “hackers" from illegally obtaining access to this information. We do not warrant or represent that your information will be protected against, loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Data Retention We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. </string>
    <string name="privacy_clause_name">PrivacyPolicy</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="reset_edit">Enter your email address</string>
    <string name="service_provision">BY INSTALLING, USING OR OTHERWISE ACCESSING THE SERVICE, YOU AGREE TO THESE TERMS OF SERVICE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS OF SERVICE, PLEASE DO NOT INSTALL, USE OR OTHERWISE ACCESS THE SERVICE. USE OF THE SERVICE IS VOID WHERE PROHIBITED.  We reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of these Terms of Service. You will be deemed to have accepted such changes by continuing to use the Service. If at any point you do not agree to any portion of the then-current version of our Terms of Service, you must immediately stop using the Service.  You shall not share the Account or the Login Information, nor let anyone else access your Account or do anything else that might jeopardize the security of your Account. You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the Login Information, and you will be responsible for all uses of the Login Information, including purchases, whether or not authorized by you. You are responsible for anything that happens through your Account.  Accounts NOTWITHSTANDING ANYTHING TO THE CONTRARY HEREIN, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU SHALL HAVE NO OWNERSHIP OR OTHER PROPERTY INTEREST IN THE ACCOUNT, AND YOU FURTHER ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT ALL RIGHTS IN AND TO THE ACCOUNT ARE AND SHALL FOREVER BE OWNED BY AND INURE TO THE BENEFIT OF US.  Suspension and Termination of Account and Service WITHOUT LIMITING ANY OTHER REMEDIES, WE MAY LIMIT, SUSPEND, TERMINATE, MODIFY, OR DELETE ACCOUNTS OR ACCESS TO THE SERVICES OR PORTIONS THEREOF IF YOU ARE, OR we SUSPECTS THAT YOU ARE, FAILING TO COMPLY WITH ANY OF THESE TERMS OF SERVICE OR FOR ANY ACTUAL OR SUSPECTED ILLEGAL OR IMPROPER USE OF THE SERVICE, WITH OR WITHOUT NOTICE TO YOU. YOU CAN LOSE YOUR USER NAME AND PERSONA AS A RESULT OF ACCOUNT TERMINATION OR LIMITATION, AS WELL AS ANY BENEFITS, PRIVILEGES, EARNED ITEMS AND PURCHASED ITEMS ASSOCIATED WITH YOUR USE OF THE SERVICE, AND WE ARE UNDER NO OBLIGATION TO COMPENSATE YOU FOR ANY SUCH LOSSES OR RESULTS.  We reserves the right to stop offering and/or supporting the Service or a particular game or part of the Service at any time, at which point your license to use the Service or a part thereof will be automatically terminated. In such event, we shall not be required to provide refunds, benefits or other compensation to users in connection with such discontinued Services.   Fees and Purchase Terms In the Service you may purchase, with “real world” money, a limited, personal, non-transferable, non-sublicensable, revocable license to use (a) “virtual currency”, including but not limited to virtual cash or diamonds; (b) “virtual in-game items” (together with “virtual currency”, “Virtual Items”); And (c) other goods or services (“Merchandise”). You are only allowed to purchase Virtual Items from us or our authorised partners through the Service, and not in any other way.We may manage, regulate, control, modify or eliminate Virtual Items and/or Merchandise at any time, with or without notice. The transfer of Virtual Items and Merchandise is prohibited. You shall not sell, redeem or otherwise transfer Virtual Items or Merchandise to any person or entity.  ALL PURCHASES AND REDEMPTIONS OF THIRD PARTY VIRTUAL CURRENCY MADE THROUGH THE SERVICE ARE FINAL AND NON-REFUNDABLE.  Disclaimer of Warranties THE SERVICE IS PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS FOR YOUR USE, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, AND THOSE ARISING FROM COURSE OF DEALING OR USAGE OF TRADE. CENTURY HETU DOES NOT WARRANT THAT YOU WILL BE ABLE TO ACCESS OR USE THE SERVICE AT THE TIMES OR LOCATIONS OF YOUR CHOOSING; THAT THE SERVICE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE; THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED; OR THAT THE GAME OR THE SERVICE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS.  Force Majeure We shall not be liable for any delay or failure to perform resulting from causes outside the reasonable control, including without limitation any failure to perform hereunder due to unforeseen circumstances or cause beyond control such as acts of God, war, terrorism, riots, embargoes, acts of civil or military authorities, fire, floods, accidents, strikes, or shortages of transportation facilities, fuel, energy, labor or materials. </string>
    <string name="service_provision_name">TermofService</string>
    <string name="signup">Register</string>
    <string name="signup_account">Please register with your email address</string>
    <string name="signup_fail">Failed. please try again</string>
    <string name="signup_password">Password</string>
    <string name="signup_password_again">Password</string>
    <string name="signup_password_different">Passwords dont match</string>
    <string name="signup_success">Registration succeeded</string>
    <string name="signup_title">Register</string>
    <string name="tourist_login">Guest Login</string>
    <string name="user_exist_tip">Username already exists</string>
    <string name="other_account">Other account login</string>
    <string name="confirm">confirm</string>
    <string name="cancel">cancel</string>
    <string name="loading">loading</string>
    <string name="init_Success">The account does not exist</string>
    <string name="pay_for_three">Recharge platform</string>
    <string name="permission_ask">Please give me this permission, and I will be able to log in.</string>
    <string name="permission_denied">READ_PHONE_STATE Permission denied</string>
</resources>